https://siawso.org/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Loading...
Privacy Policy
Survivors of Incest Anonymous (SIAWSO) respects your privacy
SIAWSO provides this Privacy Statement to inform you of our Privacy Policy and practices, and the way your information is collected online and how it is used. We have structured our websites so that you can visit SIAWSO on the web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. We make this notice readily available on our public site, subsidiaries, and our shopping cart. Our Policy applies to all SIAWSO owned domains and the Shopping Cart. This policy also applies to all the subsidiaries (“SIAWSO sub-domains”).
Keeping your information secure
SIAWSO is committed to protecting the information you provide us. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, SIAWSO has in place appropriate physical and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect.
PayPal is used to process all credit cards, debit cards, and other PayPal transactions. They also have their own Privacy Statement.
Personal information is collected within the Shopping Cart for shipping and billing purposes only.
SIAWSO does not share any personal information with any third party.
Changes to this Statement
We may occasionally make some changes or updates to this Privacy Statement. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect your personal information.
